yaoota.com 2017-02-17

# Privacy - Yaoota!

## The Short Version (for the impatient)

If you happen to be using our website Yaoota, we may collect some information that can help us serve you better when you decide to revisit our page. We are fanatically serious about online privacy and security; therefore you can rest assured that all personal information is stored safely on our servers, and that we will not misuse your trust in our service.

We do not spam users, and we do not engage in or support spamming activities. We may use your personal information in an anonymized, non-individual-identifying form, to generate insights about the market behaviour. We may use these insights to better serve you, or allow sellers to enhance their service - all that would still be carried out in a non-individual-identifying form.

## The Full Version

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Yaoota’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Yaoota’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Yaoota may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Yaoota also collects potentially personally-identifying information like IP addresses - Yaoota does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Yaoota choose to interact with Yaoota in ways that require Yaoota to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Yaoota gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our list or review features to create a profile based on a username and email address. In each case, Yaoota maintains such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Yaoota. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that the refusal may limit them from engaging in certain website-related activities and making use of Yaoota’s full set of features/functions.

### Aggregated Statistics

Yaoota may collect data about the behavior of visitors to its website and publish non-personally-identifying information or statistics accordingly. For example, Yaoota may reveal how popular a certain product or offering is, how many times a product has been viewed or bought, or which products are popular with a certain segment of users. However, Yaoota does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Yaoota discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees or contractors (1) need to know that information in order to process it on Yaoota’s behalf or to provide services available at Yaoota’s website, and (2) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. By using Yaoota, you consent to the transfer of such information to these employees, contractors, or affiliates. Yaoota will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Yaoota discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Yaoota. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Yaoota, third parties, or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Yaoota and have supplied your email address, Yaoota may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Yaoota and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum out of respect for your inbox. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Yaoota takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Yaoota uses cookies to help Yaoota identify and track visitors, their usage of Yaoota website, and their website access preferences. Yaoota visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Yaoota’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Yaoota’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Yaoota may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Yaoota’s sole discretion. Yaoota encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Yaoota. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Yaoota will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Jurisdiction

This Privacy Statement is governed and enforced subject to the laws of the Arab Republic of Egypt.
